(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, please.
(Sheldon:)Leonard is trying to walk
a mile in my metaphorical shoes.
(Sheldon:)He can't walk in my actual shoes.
(Sheldon:)He has the feet of a toddler.
(Raj:)So, how are you gonna return the DVD
if the store went out of business?
(Leonard:)Monday morning I'll go downtown,
look up the owner's information,
(Leonard:)send him the DVD.
(Leonard:)Pay the late fee...
(Leonard:)And prove to Sheldon
that you can have a problem...
(Leonard:)And solve it...
(Leonard:)Without acting
like a complete lunatic.
Ahh!
(Howard:)And the man impersonating a bear
would like everyone to know that,
(Howard:)Only you can prevent forest fires.
(Raj:)I don't get it.
(Howard:)You didn't have
Smokey the Bear in India?
(Raj:)No. Oh, is he anything like
Mun-Mun the Mongoose?
(Raj:)He taught us not to play with cobras.
(Howard:)You had to be taught
not to play with cobras?